<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<event>
	<requirements tile.structure="City"/>
	<path option="Large City">
		<out>You enter a large city. There is a 4-star hotel, high-class bar, mayor's office, and police station</out>
			<path option="Go to Bar">
				<out>The place is bustling with activity</out>
				<path option="Buy Drink (-3 Gold)" player.gold=">2">
					<out>You sip down the drink, and feel your strength increase. (Water Restored)</out>
					<action type="player.fillWater"/>
					<action type="player.removeGold">3</action>
					<returnToMap/>
				</path>
				<path option="Buy Food (-4 Gold)" player.gold=">3">
					<out>You wolf down a well-portioned plate of food, then relax on a full stomach.</out>
					<action type="player.removeGold">4</action>
					<!-- fill food -->
					<returnToMap/>
				</path>
				<path option="You have no money. Leave." player.gold="&lt;2">
					<out>You walk out empty handed.</out>
					<returnToMap/>
				</path>
				<path option="Leave" player.gold=">1">
					<out>There's nothing you need here.</out>
					<returnToMap/>
				</path>
			</path>
			<path option="Go to Hotel">
				<out>The owner looks up from his desk. "Come, weary traveler," he says, "let's find you a room"</out>
				<path option="Get in Room (-5 gold)" player.gold=">4">
					<out>You rest exceptionally well, and when you get up, you notice several people enjoying biscuits that were set out for breakfast.</out>
					<action type="player.removeGold">4</action>
					<!-- regain health, food -->
					<returnToMap/>
				</path>
				<path option="Sleep Outside Instead">
					<out>You don't have that kind of money to spend. The manager looks on you with pity as you step out.</out>
					<path option="Sleep in Alley">
						<out>You pick out an alleyway that looks slightly better than the others, and set your head down.
Sometime in the night, you jolt awake. A man is going through your bag.</out>
						<path option="Scare Him Off">
							<out>You sit up and start moving towards him. He notices you and books down the alley.</out>
							<path option="Check Bag" player.gold=">1">
								<out>Looks like he took some of your gold. It's best to move on.</out>
								<action type="player.removeGold">2</action>
								<returnToMap/>
							</path>
							<path option="Check Bag" player.gold="&lt;2">
								<out>You are relieved to see he didn't take much. You decide it is best to leave the city</out>
								<returnToMap/>
							</path>
						</path>
						<path option="Fight Him">
							<out>You quickly stand up and raise your fists. He notices you and runs the opposite direction.</out>
							<path option="Check Bag">
								<out>You scared him off before he could take anything. Regardless, you think it's time to leave the city.</out>
								<returnToMap/>
							</path>
						</path>
					</path>
					<path option="Sleep in Woods">
						<out>Besides the terrible back cramps you sleep fine out in the nearby woods.</out>
						<returnToMap/>
					</path>
				</path>
			</path>
			<path option="See Mayor">
				<out>You stroll up to city hall, and notice a large demonstration and a heavy police presence</out>
				<path option="Leave">
					<out>You don't want any part in what might go down.</out>
					<returnToMap/>
				</path>
			</path>
			<path option="Go to Police">
				<out>You walk into the police station.</out>
				<path option="Talk to Receptionist">
					<out>You attempt to talk to the receptionist. He seems to have at least two people on hold and is frantically writing down notes from a third conversation.
"Unless it's an emergency, get lost. We are very busy". You don't see the point in sticking around.</out>
					<returnToMap/>
				</path>
				<path option="Sneak About">
					<out>You make it about halfway down the hall before you are arrested.</out>
					<gameOver/>
				</path>
				<path option="Leave">
					<out>There's nothing you need here.</out>
					<returnToMap/>
				</path>
			</path>
			<path option="Leave">
				<out>You've seen enough of this city.</out>
				<returnToMap/>
			</path>
		</path>
</event>
